Tea,
try to stay quiet, black, you
deserve it, people,
try not to disturb dear people, and
so on,
[ __ ], Litvin, Maksimov, relax,
please, my mouth, demolish my small smile,
like Xiaomi,
relax, eyelids, wormwood, RST, and
Michael Irby,
slightly pull in your stomach, shooter, bracket, teams,
shoulders back, a little,
fingers relaxed, back very
straight,
Fariz, wine, and a relaxed forehead, eyelid,
relax yourself, and stand with your index
finger and thumb almost touching
each other.
We will do a meditation dance, and you
will have two parts. In the first part,
the warm-up is not the meditation itself, then we will
take a break from us, but then we
will travel to our past
lives. So let's focus on the sounds of the
air conditioner
[music].
Place your mind on the sound of the air conditioner,
and at night, just as you put
your head on the pillow, and on RST, you are very
relaxed, very joyful, I
want to place my ears on the
air conditioner, too, so let's go,
please come to do, so we have been seen, and
he has blue eyes for this.  Orsha,
now please go to the sound of
the heartbeat.
Feel how your heart beats in your chest
with each exhalation. Please exhale
a little extra air.
Try to completely empty your lungs and
take a normal breath. There is
no end. Now let's go
inside our heart.
In cialis, on top of the cast iron, and inside your
heart there is a beautiful room for
meditation and computers.   A
very comfortable meditation cushion, nice
with me, pleasant sunlight and fresh
air. It
seems strange in the room. The
perimeter of this room was given. The walls
beat a little because it is our
heart.
Yes, you are pulled by the world on the people in my
insides.
Now let's imagine that inside
this meditation room there is
another room for children's meditation, a sink, and it is
even quieter there.
Danish inside. Let's go inside
this inner room. A
chair, the nation itself, also has plenty of
sunlight and fresh air. We also take
long, long exhalations. Mark 1 diamond. Go
out to the river. It's very quiet there, and we
almost don't hear the heartbeat. A quieter
place.
This is not either. In some places, next to me, there is a
small table. We drag it. We demand a
meditation table.
Is it a small pair of Anna's figures? On it is a
small sugar bowl. They
lower the sugar bowl. The ring finger of
my left hand, Lind leading inside, is covered with granulated sugar.
All the guests of the zone are written off, and a small,
tiny crystal of sugar remains on the
finger, but this is oh, here from the hands of wine in
fireworks. I'm glad of this, single sand, and inside
this, sugar crystals, it would be so
quiet. Hand inside.  I'll go inside, and we'll
catch
the insights of the figure. The song is placed inside
this sugar crystal. A whole small
window
in the pension here is a cross and a small
cat opens. Sugar crystals are
my main quiz. It's inside. Oh, it penetrates inside. Inside,
crumbling bigmir and
shoes from the inside. Surprise. A large room
for meditation.
Matzah from above with me. Comments before suicide.
Crystal.
Beautiful sunlight penetrates through the
walls of the crystal. Morituri. This is a very
comfortable and convenient room for
meditation on the number. Fresh air inside
under the match. Mother, gentlemen. It's much quieter.
Now let's stretch it out. I found it. We'll
make our mind very big. Evil inside.
To the surprise here. And so on, three
sugar crystals, my wild supersets, coffee. My mind
becomes a Pacific Ocean of expertise and
stretches in all directions, and a gas tank
and goes very deep down, and all this is mine.
Amazing steel insights. The figure of the cross, and
incredibly, for all this, inside, a granule of
sugar went out. You're full, and coffee is the whole Pacific
Ocean. Bye, my bike. It's very quiet. Troubles
and very deep
on my. My sister cleans endlessly, money,
now we mind.  also spreads over the
entire blue sky above the ocean, very
high, its calling and
as wide as the ocean on my mondes,
mathematician, now my mind is much, much
more frozen, insights, the figure of the cross, and still it's
all inside, granulated sugar,
and you're home to, and it will be even quieter,
look for the step of an internet meme, if I completely
turned off my site, we have exactly the same way
as I turn off the lights at home, to
control this, 2, I can turn off
the switch with Danila's eyes and the light
turns off,
try, let's try to do
this with our mind, three notes burn out,
network mayn't, we turn off the switch
of ours, if after that thoughts arise
[music],
lush, we'll look at them and push them out,
and so turn off the light,
note, and the price is mine, no thoughts, you,
Persian, just on, if thoughts
arise, push them out,
power, and the last step is smoke and 2 kopecks, and then we'll
take a break and wine, an
even quieter place, art online,
deception, we turn off the light of our minds and
remain very, very quiet, and heights, and
even if a thought arises
Arnold, I'll ignore them,
let these thoughts come
and go,
romance, Bardem, and just don't think about
them. So let's go.
You're not retired. You can open your eyes. Stretch out and get a
drink of something if you need it urgently.
I ate. You can go with Bobik. Fe new,
but we'll continue.
[music] [music]
[music]
with
her
[music]
but to his steel, he has anti-cheat.
So we'll continue. There was no break.
I don't look at
how
steel is like. So we'll begin.
Please, sit down.
Explorer.
And so we'll go through the research
based on the research of our past life. And I'll
leave. And so, take it. I'm right there, pressing on him.
Try not to move. Try
not to move. Fila, coffee. If you feel like
you want to cough,
focus on the spot where it tickles
in your throat.
Take a cup of coffee and then the cough will go away.
Snowboard. Let's first focus
on breathing. Do 10 cycles.
Long exhalations.
Nolitsin. Catch and save a little and
choose.
Now let's invite your teacher to
come.  Meditate with us, yes,
of course, your great first
teachers are mom and dad, buy, and we
had great teachers at school, or the person
who taught me my job, or you
can also invite I will, or any other
famous person, whom you
love cheese, and your number is very happy and
sits down to meditate next to you with
hoes, and we will meditate together.
Question: Your teacher is not a statue, but a
real person, and looks at you with his eyes, with his eyes, with
us, your eyes are
closed, your teacher's eyes are open, and
the teacher looks at you with great love
and the truth about the world, you and taught, are very
proud that you meditate, Danish
Tess, and let's try to see this
person very clearly,
domain of the date from St. Petersburg, barista,
top quanta, pretty, release,
now let's think about something we
like about our teacher,
some good quality that we
love him, dear, maybe your teacher is
very patient and never gets angry,
we are shot with binoculars,
or maybe your teacher loves to
work hard and help other people, chose
from you skates, we pour, maybe your
teacher always takes care of sick
people,
voodoo people, or maybe  Your teacher
always cares about the court and the Goban of the
elderly, and you yourself are not qualified and have no attitude and were
taken away in New York, the Aquarius
disk, think of some one
good quality
your tormentors adore in him
and the line
that you yourself want to develop in yourself,
varios, and how many lari and mothers, why do
I see this good quality in my
teacher and through DNS, a teacher is also
like a pen
in Russian, Francis,
well, what I see comes from my
own seeds, sentido burfitt video,
I must have planted the seeds to
see this wonderful quality in my
teacher and twitter, water bible,
if, for example, teachers like to help
elderly people,
if I see this in my teachers,
admins, but we say this means that a long time
ago I planted these seeds in my
mind and this means that I helped many
elderly people, a cube of 2 layers, a cube based on, maybe
in this life, maybe a
past life,
most of us cannot remember our
past life, but I can guess
what I was doing, a certain one, helping
elderly people, because my teacher
likes to help elderly people, so
I  I'll pretend that I can get into my
past life as a fighter in a group. I can
imagine
myself helping other people. Maybe
it was a hundred years ago.
Maybe I lived in another country
and spoke a different language. Maybe my
face and body were completely different.
Maybe I was a man or a woman
or even a bird or a fish. But I was taking care
of the elderly
late. So let's dive into my
past life. At the end, let's
pretend that we can see our
past life and create a movie of this
past life.
Try to see a lot of details and
have fun. We're just pretending,
but even imagination, pretending,
comes from seeds, and so on.
Enjoy it. But I can be number one.
New tracks. A little longer. And
after that, there will be a break.
[music]
Ours.
Please come back again.
Look at your teacher.
Thank him or her for being there
and where they came from.
Dollars like armadas. Smolin. We
created a lot of good karma this morning. The
best way to protect this karma is to
share it with other people. So I
took three long breaths, like a gray
arus
salad, nose out, and with each breath.  I will send
these seeds to
dear people tonight. We will
make a fire offering with the smoke from this
fire for a month. We will also make
offerings of our seeds to the
whole world. Mobis, so there will be peace.
So let's take three long exhalations.
After all, the axial language is golden. Each exhalation is a
golden light
that spreads throughout the world.
These good seeds bring happiness to
other people and Danish.
Well, you understood. Slowly open your
eyes.
Let's stretch.
We'll take a break before the first one. If
anyone has a question about this meditation on the
microphone.
I want to understand the difference between meditation and
sleep. Sometimes it looks the same as if
sleep and meditation look very similar.
Good question. And in both houses and dorms
there are five types of physical things. Fendi
ends. Things that you can
see and hear. Feel smells,
taste, and can feel girls, and you can
feel skin touches. FMS.
And this comes from seeds. We
can really touch the microphone with a virus. We can
hear sounds. Other houses, but in both dorms there
is another physical form.
Chiki-chiki soup is called Cheki Jae Sook.
This is a special physical form.  example
and for example honey if I imagine being
Olaf the big elephant while you are Stoletova
the color of two heads does not actually
exist in the world I can imagine
then in school both darmas without language it is
real it is like a real thing because it
also comes from your seeds
therefore the pictures that you see in
meditation about your past life and the
pictures that you see in a dream
system both darmas landings are all
real physical things in the future but there is a
difference in motivation
all the food comes from motivation and in
meditation
cupid ordinary properties our motivation is
very strong cabbage purposefully
we see pictures we create pictures
[music]
engine in a dream there is no great motivation wine
and wine and in the teachings of ethics they say that
if you have a dream and in a dream you
kill a person inch do
you create a pocket and the answer is
practically no because in a dream you
can not control anything but
meditation we have a lot of motivation we
purposefully create an image and
[music]
according to the school both darmas tempike
image in a dream
real physical suddenly languages ​​they are
called mental and physical but no
one  great motivation, but in
meditation we try to see something
important, and the image in meditation sows
very powerful seeds
because it comes from within the mind and c
thinks, and inside the mind is where
the heart is, the most powerful seeds are, sleep is also
mental, the image is not
such a strong motivation, there is no
strong emotion, meditation sowed very
powerful seeds, the most powerful seeds for
you, he does not sow very many seeds, be stupid,
and both are mental images,
well, I'll
weaken, you have my suit, one more question,
you choose, thank you, teacher,
during my meditation I saw many
images,
some of them from you, shows that I
saw, some of them from the Chinese
dynasty, there were a lot of pictures, I tried to
concentrate, but I couldn't
concentrate at all,
pictures just flashed all the time, good
question, and after the break, we will
continue reading the book by
Indigo Litvak, God willing, and it will
talk about where
negative emotions come from, often this comes
from the films we have seen, every time
we watch something, we sow seeds,
so it is better not to watch too much
TV if we watch these films
where people kill other people a lot we
actually relax we are not
trying to kill anyone and I like to
go to the movies take a break
relax yeah forget it's good
juwel nax
valves and hammer at home acts 2k
relaxing properly is an
important darma activity if you
work all the time work work
loves you will get tired and you will become so
easily irritated
start arguing with other people not dead
fighters
and sow bad seeds very bad
teeth and lax and so relax and
settle down enjoy
going to the beach make a big fire 2-3
hours relax
very good meditation
so going to the movies is good sometimes
relax very good but choose the
movie carefully
carefully - when I was a
kid we had four
Allman brothers and one mother and work she was a
school teacher decisively bridge well in
Arizona that's the most low-paying
job so we didn't have money to
go to the movies in the sky once or twice a year
then I grew up the natives began to
give everyone red envelopes I have a
lot of money and but now I
go to the movies quite often I go with
my  Veronica's partner, competition, and
since I couldn't
watch a movie as a child, now I go to any movie
theater. I don't care if it's a love
story or fantasy or murder. It
feels special to me to
go because I couldn't
walk when I was little, and
Veronica and I go to the movies, and if they start
killing people, about a year old, she takes me by the
hand and says, "Let's go." Other people,
what are you doing there?
She's on fire. We leave. The feeling that she
refuses to watch the murder. Achilles
was there, and you, it actually irritates me a little.
For me, it's normal. Murder
is diamonds. It's a movie. No, it's
bad. 7 and 8. And even just watching it.
His ways with a name, then you'll already sow
seeds with you. When I did a three-year
silent retreat, of the month, after
six months of meditation with pure ones,
very strange things happened. I
heard a sound and thought it would sound as if someone were
talking to me
very quietly
[music]. There will be
and this rim. They were talking to me
about the coat of arms.
I put it even more quietly for victory. What is this?
When I was five years old, you told me about this.
Enforce, wait, there was a
spaghetti and Wesson commercial on TV. There was a song about
spaghetti.
I haven't thought about it for 50 years, but it doesn't occur to you.
This isn't happening. I'm trying.
This was a TV commercial
50 years ago. So, everything you watch is
in front of them and remains in your mind.
When you do a retreat, you realize
that you are him.
Everything you watched remains in your mind.
So, be careful and don't
necessarily go to the movies where
people and Candida, like all McDonald's, are
all over movies with violence
in front of them. This is a hand, all the bad
influence from America. Candida Malton.
McDonald's. This is only diabetes. It gives your
children information about this and don't let children eat
these things.
Think they're a year and two old. Don't let
them go
watch a violent film. Edgar D. They
achieved this moment. This gives them mental health problems.
Diabetes is fraught. Try it this year.
Find a movie. Go to the movies, but
watch nice companies utilizing the file and
inspiring ones. Good, thank you.